GABRIELLA MORGAN

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

■ gabriellarosemorgan@gmail.com **③** gabriellapelton.com **५** (940) 448-0755 **♀** Denton, TX **in** gabriella-pelton **♠** gabbypelton

SUMMARY

Full stack web developer skilled in MERN, React Native, and .NET. With more than five years of professional experience in business development and consulting prior to coding, I excel at breaking down problems and collaborating to solve them effectively.

SKILLS

FRONT-END: .NET, HTML, CSS, JS, React, React Native, Redux, Vue

BACK-END: SQL, MongoDB, Node, .NET

EMPLOYMENT

Inputs.Ag, *Co-Founder/CTO*, California/Texas

Mar. 2021 - Current

- Inputs is a procurement platform built with Independent Consultants and Farmers in mind.
- · Our model allows consultants to build invoices with products from dozens of manufacturers at factory direct prices
- · Invoices are emailed directly to farms, who can then pay using any of several convenient methods
- App is built from scratch to meet the unique needs of the agricultural industry

Alkami Technology, Software Engineer II, .NET, Dallas, TX

July 2020 - Mar. 2021

- Full Stack Developer building .NET applications for an enterprise fintech company
- Developed features, resolved bugs, reviewed PRs in an Agile/Scrum environment

Ambit Energy/Vistra Energy, *Software Developer V - Retail Technology*

Aug. 2018 - Mar. 2020

- · Full Stack Developer working with React/React Native, Net Framework, Microsoft SQL, and numerous front-end frameworks
- Began as contractor, promoted to full-time Software Developer I, then to Software Developer II
- Built mobile app features from scope call to app store release
- Participated in daily scrums, sprint planning, and cross-team collaboration on company-spanning projects affecting millions of users

PROJECTS

Mar. 2021 - Current Inputs.Ag

- Inputs is a procurement platform built with Independent Consultants and Farmers in mind.
- Built with MERN and deployed with Netlify/Heroku
- A live product processing real payments and iterating in 2-week agile sprints

DriveFair Mar. 2020 - Current

- DriveFair is a web and mobile application designed to facilitate restaurants, drivers, and customers with food delivery
- Built with Node, Express, MongoDB, React, and React Native
- Stripe-integrated and ready to take real users and payments
- A solo project brought from idea to MVP-complete in 60 days

MvAmbit Mobile Aug. 2018 - Mar. 2020

- MyAmbit Mobile is the mobile application for Ambit customers
- Built with React Native (with native modules) and .NET
- Contributed all new feature development for 2019 and addressed numerous issues that represented the bulk of user complaints

EDUCATION

Lambda School Jan. 2018 - Aug. 2018

Computer Science Full Stack Web Development 2018

Lambda School is a Computer Science & Software Engineering Academy that provides an immersive hands-on curriculum with a focus on computer science fundamentals, software engineering, and web development.